Kresten, it's your father.
Welcome Marie.
Thank you.
How nice to see you.
You too.
Say hello to your uncle, Peter.
I'd better see to go.
So do not lose your place on the stage.
Are not you going with us?
Uh, no.
Peter likes to stay
in the city once in a while.
You not only look like them.
You also sound like them.
You will also learn.
Do as he says.
Are there many animals?
Yes, there are many different animals.
There are foxes, there are bears, there are deer.
Are there bears where we live?
Where we live?
No, there's  no bears.
But if there was one ...
Then we shoot it and and sell it down in the city.
Is there a town nearby?
Yeah, not so far from us.
We can go there one day.
Kresten ...
You shouldn't be worried, alright?
It's a really nice place.
And I've built is so there's room for all of us.
Can we really go out hunting?
Actually, we can tomorrow.
If you want.
Marie, take a sip.
It's a local custom here.
My wife and my son did, yes.
I've been here a while.
Bite his ear.
Marie, bite his ear.
Do not be afraid.
Kresten, pick the gun up.
Don't be afraid.
Just take it.
And stay down, Kresten.
No, stay down. Stay down, Kresten!
Who did it?
I have not seen them before.
Strangers.
I'll go and talk to the sheriff.
See you in a bit.